Lamon Zhao

Senior FullStack Developer



Thailand

A highly focused Senior FullStack Developer with 6+ years of experience in a variety of development projects. Organized, methodical and a keen eye for detail results in solid coding and a trustworthy program. Understanding client requirements and communicating the progress of projects are core values in achieving long-lasting business relationships.

I provide Front-End, Back-End and also user-friendly web solutions. I would like to inform you that I am highly skilled with frontend & backend frameworks and libraries like React.js, Angular, Vue.js, PHP, Node.js, Python, DevOps and so on, as I have handsome experience of it. Still, I am always eager to learn a new thing and make my skills sharper whenever I get a chance.

Above and beyond, I have a great passion for blockchain & cryptocurrency like web3.js, Dapp, De-Fi, NFT etc and software technology as well.





Work Experience

Dapp Developer | Ora Apps

Jul.2022 - Oct.2022

As a Dapp Developer, Created the main website and multiple mobile applications -ICO, DEX, LaunchPad and Gambling websites using modern technologies. Final goal is just publishing the De-Fi solution along with our token and NFTs. experienced engineer led web3.js integration stuff with detailed guidelines under the strict review.

FullStack Engineer | Seidat Inc

May.2021 – Jul.2022

Senior Web Developer who was working on Meteor.js + React.js project based on the Nx monorepo architectured project. Resolved several technical problems and integrated Pipedriver and other third party services into the existing platform. Worked under very strict code review.

Frontend Developer | Taks Inc(Company closed in 2022)

Oct.2019 - Mar.2021

Designed and developed a distributed solution for a Ticket management service using React.js and Java Spring framework. Developed an Android/iOS application available on the Play Store and App Store. Published desktop applications which can be run on different platforms, and published it to the Microsoft App Store. Implemented a web application that allowed third-party vendors to integrate and manage their calendars in a single place, with controllable widgets.

FullStack Engineer | ShipEZ Inc

Sep.2017 – Jul.2019

Developed a web app to manage active building maintenance from scratch. Fixed bugs and implemented new features per the requirements, under the technical guidance of the CTO. Meteor.js and Angular were the main technologies we built as an admin panel for musicians and artists who's not familiar with Linkedin and other online job platforms. Having such a large number of registered users from different countries. CEO was also a singer and songwriter.

Education

Bangkok University

Computer science

2014 - 2017

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science and Technology

Skills

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript / TypeScript
- Angular
- React.js
- Vue.js
- Aurelia Framework
- Svelt.js
- Next.js
- Nuxt.js
- Meteor.js
- PHP
- Codelgniter
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Nest.js
- Express.js
- Ionic Framework
- React Native
- Python / Django
- Flask
- Java
- Java Spring Frameworks
- Rust
- Golang
- Echo(Go)
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

- GitHub
- BitBucket
- GitLab
- SVN
- AWS
- Heroku
- GCP
- Vagrant
- GraphQL
- Elastic Search
- NX
- Monorepo
- Testing(unit, e2e, ab)
- Electron
- NGRX
- Apollo
- State Management
- Docker
- Solidity
- Smart Contract
- Tokenomics
- NFT marketplace
- DEX
- DeFi
- Remix
- Truffle
- Hardhat
- Opensea